All pirates searching for the treasure One Piece
must brave the second half of the Grand Line.
These wild and dangerous seas are known as the New World.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body became rubber
after eating the gum gum fruit,
sets sail into the New World with his faithful crew.
I'm gonna be the king of the pirates!
Two years have passed since the War of the Best
and Marineford.
Luffy and his crew underwit special training
before reuniting to continue on to the New World.
They are now separated once again on Fishman Island,
thousands of feet below sea level.
Let's go!
Break through!
We're off to the sea forest!
The Ryugu Palace in shock!
The kidnapping of Shirahoshi!
Thank you for making the trip.
I don't get many visitors from above.
No problem!
When Tom told me his kid brother back home was also a shipwright,
I knew I had to visit.
Still, traveling to Fishman Island's a pretty difficult task.
Heh, it's not bad.
Training with Tom since I was young paid off.
My crewmates and I made it here on a ship that I built!
Is that so?
Well, you were my brother's pupil.
It must be a fine vessel.
Yeah!
The Thousand Sunny will take us anywhere we want to go!
It's my life's work, my masterpiece!
I'd love to see it before you leave.
Yeah, about that.
After we got to Fishman Island,
the Sunny was swept away by the tide.
It's one of the reasons I came to see you.
You know the area much better than I do.
You have any idea where the ship might have turned up?
Trust me, you'll find it.
But where do I even start?
It's a funny thing, but when ships sink around these parts,
the tide almost always carries them to the same place.
The Sunny is bound to be there too, I guarantee it.
With gusto, even.
You're that confident, huh?
Don't worry, we'll get there soon enough.
On to the sea forest.
The sea forest?
Hold on, Luffy, what are you doing?
Stop!
Megalo, come back here now!
Stay in the palace!
Father, brothers, all my caretakers, forgive me.
I'm leaving without your permission.
I promise to be home by dinner.
We're on an adventure!
What has gotten into Megalo?
I can't believe it, he even left the doors open.
What if something were to happen to...
Oh no!
Hey, Skeleton, hurry up and check on the princess.
All right, stop writing my bones about it.
She's gone!
Princess Shirohoshi never leaves her room!
Oh no!
But why are you keeping her locked up here in the first place?
To keep her safe!
Enemies are trying to get to her!
Kidnap you!
I'm sorry I failed you.
Who knows how far away the kidnappers are!
Kidnappers?
Princess Shirohoshi!
Forgive me!
You're positive she was kidnapped?
Huh?
Huh!
How rude of you!
Ah!
The gate connecting Fishman Island to the Ryugu Palace.
Tell us where the switch to open it is or else.
Wait, switch?
Skeleton!
You have to get back to King Nepune as fast as possible!
Tell him the princess is gone, and that we're under attack!
We didn't want any of this to happen, but it's the only way.
They told us that if we want to survive, we've got to follow their orders.
Please, just tell us, okay?
Whose orders?
It doesn't matter!
Just tell us so we're all gonna die!
I don't...
Just tell us!
What in the world is going on here?
What in the world is going on here!
Again, count.
Unfortunately, we'll crack on the Juse Woody.
How'd you make this?
How can you see them?
We'll give you...
Ah!
Professional Monkey is...
I've lost sightseeing.
These guys are...
So useless!
Humans really are pathetic, aren't they...
Put them in the water and they just drown!
You pirates are now under the control of Horty Jones, so listen closely.
I've got wonderful news.
You have the chance to be part of a historic mission.
Talk about lucky.
That looks like Van Der Decken.
Isn't he the captain of the Flying Dutchman?
This can't be real.
That cursed ghost ship is a myth.
Oh, I'm no ghost.
But I am Van Der Decken's descendant.
I've got a curse of my own as well.
Even though I'm a fishman, I can't swim.
But that's all right.
I've got this devil fruit power known as the Mark Mark fruit.
How about I show you?
You and the stripes.
Come here.
Step right up.
Me?
Horty!
Yeah.
This is nonsense and you know it.
Enough is enough.
Is that Horty?
What is he doing here?
Hello there.
Those energy steroids you're taking will do nothing but mess up your body.
And no good can come of destroying Fishman Island.
On top of it, you're underestimating the power of Neptune.
Horty.
I've heard enough of your rambling.
I don't want to listen to your voice anymore.
To think you were an officer of the pirate group that I admired.
Now you're nothing but a washed up coward.
So, make way for the real pirates.
If we want to teach all of the humans a lesson, we're going to need Fishman Island.
That means Neptune is our enemy.
Arlong thought Fishman were the supreme race.
When did you change your mind?
Arlong was wrong.
There is no supreme race.
Deacon?
Hyozo, why are you doing this?
The two of you refused to help Arlong invade the East Blue when he was in power.
So tell me, what makes you want to work with these young punks now?
That's easy.
I meant it for money.
These guys are willing to pay.
Arlong was stingy.
He never did pony up enough dough to enlist my services.
That's why he was always stuck taking crappy swordsmen like you, Along.
No wonder he lost.
A sight for sore eyes.
An angry Hachi.
Yeah, I remember what happened back then.
Arlong had the nerve to ask me to work underneath him.
What a preposterous idea.
Vander Decken never works under anybody.
I'm my own man.
Hordy gets that better than anyone.
Arlong had goals and an ability to act on them, which I can respect.
But he was also brash.
As a leader, he was lacking in cunning.
When you old-timers were running rampant on the sea, we were all still too young to become pirates.
So we watched.
We saw what you did well and what you did poorly.
We learned from all your mistakes.
In that sense, we owe you our thanks.
Take heart.
I will continue right where Arlong left off.
I don't understand why you're not on board with that.
You supported Arlong for all those years, after all.
What a disappointment you are, Hachi.
You might want to know.
The pirate who destroyed Arlong's dream, Straw Hat Luffy, is on Fishman Island.
It's a perfect opportunity for some revenge.
Even though I fought him as a member of the Arlong Pirates, he now calls me his friend.
Look!
All three of you are my friends now!
Straw Hat Luffy also saved my life.
If I could, I would see him.
But I'm too ashamed of my fellow Fishman to do it!
How can I face him when you're clinging to Arlong's legacy?
You consider a human your friend?
How pathetic!
You're not a real fishman!
Get out of my sight!
Calm yourself and listen.
You may have forgotten how pirates do things around here.
If there's something you want to say, you've got to use violence to get your point across.
For example!
Watch!
Where is he throwing it to?
Did you notice when I touched you earlier,
I marked you as my new target!
No matter what I throw or where I throw it,
it will always make its way back to whatever I mark.
Not only that, but it'll come back at you full speed!
I suspect!
But that's crazy!
Deacon just tossed the knife away from that guy!
And it came back to hit him!
The mark mark curse!
Of course, there are some limitations.
Can you figure them out?
You had better hurry.
Stay away from me, Deacon!
I've heard enough stories about your mark mark power!
You've got to make him stop!
He's trying to kill me!
Please stop him, Hordy!
Sorry, Hachi.
I can't.
As he told you earlier,
Vander Deacon isn't working under me.
We're allies on equal footing.
Besides,
you're really starting to get on my nerves.
Go ahead, Deacon!
I'll be okay if I can just find my way to the exit!
There, I should be safe now.
Hopefully, they sink in the water.
They burst through the bubble like it was nothing!
Get away!
Oh!
Ah!
To be continued...
But yet, I can throw weapons and even my love, they'll track you down to the furthest depths of hell.
That's the Mark Mark curse for you.
Whoa. He can keep stalking the princess for as long as he wants.
And stay right here. Best of all, he'll never have to deal with fighting Neptune and his sons.
Bingo!
How devious can you get?
Now, about you human pirates.
I'm sure you're all familiar with Deccan's Mark Mark power.
So, let's begin the first stage of your mission.
They say the Ryugu Palace is impregnable, but I disagree.
Someone in this room has been able to break through its defenses for ten straight years.
Him, Captain Vander Deccan.
Bah! Ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
So, you'll be our cannon fodder.
Meaning, Deccan will treat your bodies as living ammunition.
Throwing you straight into the wall of the princess's tower.
Of course, weapons can't smash it.
And most of you runts won't do any better.
And then, you'll open up the gate from inside the palace.
Find the gate switch and let us in.
That's all you have to do.
No way! We can't make it that far!
You're crazy!
We'd already be dead from hitting the wall!
You're correct.
That's why I want you humans to do it.
Your lives don't mean anything to me.
In our world, you're either slaves or corpses.
Those of you who survived the impact, carry out your duty.
If you succeed in opening the gate, I'll set you free.
But if you refuse to do it, then leave!
I'll get you out of the bubble myself.
So you better do as I say.
But if... if we leave the bubble, we can't get to the top without drowning!
Well, that's no good.
On the upside, that should make this decision easy for you, though!
Huh?
Have fun!
It's a new era.
From now on, our people will forge a new history with our own hands.
We'll start by conquering the Ryugu kingdom!
Yeah!
Shira Hoshi, just you wait!
Meanwhile, back at the palace...
Don't go so fast!
We're injured!
Pick up the pace, skeleton!
It's imperative we make it to the king!
Listen, I'm begging you to take us to that gate!
Party's gonna kill us all if we don't get it open!
You have to!
Hey, I have a question for you guys.
Sanji, go back to bed!
No fighting!
I'm not fighting.
I just want to ask them something about the Ryugu palace.
Is she there?
The mermaid princess?
Yeah.
She's there.
So what?
I'll go.
It's worth it.
No, it isn't!
You're still too weak!
If she's beautiful, you might die!
Come on.
Of course she's beautiful, right?
Well, I've never seen her.
But they do say she's quite lovely.
She is?
Right!
Then lead the way!
Let's stop fighting!
Take me!
Wait, which way is the palace?
My true love awaits!
What's wrong with this guy?
I don't know, but we're supposed to take him in regardless.
Before we depart for the palace, we need to handcuff you.
If I can see her, who cares?
Tie me up and take me away!
You nutcase!
Snap out of it!
Don't go with them!
Wait a minute!
How am I supposed to cook for the mermaid princess
if you put me in handcuffs, you imbeciles?
That's why it's not okay!
I knew he would resist!
Everyone subdue the human!
Bastards.
Sabotaging my one chance to see the princess?
I bet you're just jealous!
Too bad!
It can't help me!
Hey, Sanji!
Don't fight them!
We gotta run!
Or whatever.
Beat them all up.
Sure.
Did you realize we were innocent before you did that?
Well, it's their fault for trying to handcuff me.
Their members are the Strollhats.
How dangerous.
Look at what you've done!
Now everybody's giving us that dead fish stare!
And not because they're fishmen either!
That's not our problem.
Besides, they saw the guards attack us.
But you were the one doing all the attacking!
Hey now, you beat up a lot of them too.
Speaking of, good job.
Your training really paid off.
Oh, you think you can buy me off with a compliment?
No way, pal.
A lady is in need!
Oh my god, there's a man covered with blood on the shore!
That guy from the fishman district!
What happened to you?
Someone call a doctor!
Oh, hey!
I'm a doctor!
What?
Hachi?
Who did this?
What happened?
Hachi, it's us!
Chopper and Sanji!
Hold on!
We'll help you!
Why would someone do this?
It's you guys!
I'm happy to see you!
Is Straw Hat here too?
He's not with us!
Don't try to move!
I'll start treating you in a sec!
Wherever your friends are, find them!
And get the hell out of here!
You don't want to get involved, believe me!
Get back on your boat and leave this place while you still can!
Or you'll be fighting for your lives!
Hordeon!
Deccan!
Go!
The new fishman pirates will start attacking the whole island soon!
And once they do, the Ryugu kingdom will fall!
King Neptune!
The princess has been kidnapped!
I don't know how, but they must have broken into the room!
Also, pirates are crashing into the tower!
It's bizarre!
In any case, they'll be here any minute!
Get ready!
Kidnapped?
Somebody's taken away my Shirahoshi?
Who was it?
I'll kill them!
Wait, there's a pirate raid going on?
And they don't mean us?
This is the worst time!
All I want is to get out of here and now it's some kind of pirate party!
We're screwed!
Fine!
Just ignore me!
Jerk!
I'll cut them!
Violence is the last thing we need right now!
If we want to make it out of here alive, we have to open up the gate, no matter what!
Oh no, they're here!
You can come out of the shark now, you know!
Oh, that's okay, I think I'd rather stay inside for now!
Must be nice after being cooped up for ten years!
Yes, my heart is racing!
They're probably worried sick about me!
You've been out five minutes!
Have a little fun, would ya?
Jeez, what a weirdo!
Now I know how it feels!
This is a real adventure, huh?
It sure is!
If your heart's racing, it counts as an adventure!
You mentioned a thing called the Sea Forest, right?
So what is that?
Is it a pretty cool place?
It's a graveyard...
Or rather, there's one grave that I never got to visit because I was locked away.
Ten years I've wanted to go, and now my only dream can finally come true!
It's already been ten long years since her assassination in broad daylight threw Fishman Island into upheaval.
Time flies.
The princes have grown into strong and worthy protectors.
Princess Shirahoshi is locked in the tower, but she is safe.
But as for you, your memory survives.
Your ideals will live on forever.
Queen Otoime.
Horty's plan for revenge is set into motion.
The defenses of the Ryugu Palace have been left wide open thanks to the unexpected actions of the pirates thrown into its walls.
The Straw Hats, who had unwittingly taken control of the palace, must now defend it against the new Fishman Pirates, who pour into its halls, led by Horty himself.
On the next One Piece, Horty's Onslaught, the retaliatory plan set into motion, I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!